people to think about this [ __ ] And I
don't work here. Um, the point is
focusing on what you really care about
is what we don't do. Small consistent
effort is what we don't do. We don't
like to be bored. We don't like to think
we're going nowhere. And when you're not
getting sugar and you're only trained on
mountains of
sugar, you're not going to reward
yourself for the right things. And
that's something I try to iterate over
and over is that I don't think our
media, I don't think our fellow people
reward the right behavior. I think we
reward things accidentally. Maybe we
don't recognize how much we reinforce so
much behavior that in
retrospect we so abhorently